International Brotherhood of Sleeping Car Porters Oral History Collection OH 021
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
International Brotherhood of Sleeping Car Porters Oral History Collection
undated
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
OH 021
1 Linear Feet 1 boxes
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open wihtout restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Materials found in collection; provenance is unknown. The accession number associated with this collection is 1950.093.
General
No release forms assoicated with this collection
Scope and Contents
See BobCat, NYU's online catalog (http://bobcat.nyu.edu), for a description of this collection. The tapes are open for research but copyright is held by Schomburg Center, NYPL, and researchers should apply there for permission to quote. Index available in repository.
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers. Materials not yet digitized will need to have access copies made before they can be used. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
- Esther Crawford, Oct 19, 1988 (Box Access Audio 1, Carton 8)
- Isiah Culbreath, Oct 19, 1988 (Cassette 10)
- Israte Curtis, Dec 16, 1988 (Cassette 7)
- Ish Flory, Nov 27, 1988; cuid489 (Cassette 2A-B, Box Access Audio 1, Cd 2A-B)
- Harry Hawkins, OCt 18, 1988 (Cassette 15)
- Robert Henderson, Oct 20, 1988 (Cassette 9A-B)
- James Jackson, Dec 10, 1988 (Cassette 11A-B)
- Edward Brown Jewel, Dec 4, 1988 (Cassette 12A-C)
- Amos Kimble, Dec 9, 1988 (Cassette 5A-B)
- Elizabeth Lucas, Sep 2, 1988 (Cassette 1, Box Access Audio 1)
- Elijah Shoemaker, Dec 27, 1988 (Cassette 4A-C)
- Charles Simmons, Oct 15, 1988 (Cassette 16A-B)
- Berry Slater, Oct 16, 1988 (Cassette 14A-B)
- Fred Smith, Nov 25, 1988 (Cassette 3A-B)
- George Smith, Dec 12, 1988 (Carton 13A-B)
- Arthur Woolfolk, Oct 21, 1988 (Cassette 6A-B)